all right good morning I think everyone
早上好，我想大家
can hear me I can hear myself quite well
可以听见我，我听得很好
i'm lucas butter and in the next 45
我是卢卡斯黄油，接下来的45岁
minutes i would like to show you what
分钟，我想告诉你什么
happens under a hood when you evil
当你邪恶时发生在引擎盖下
invoke a parallel stream so the idea is
调用并行流，这样的想法是
to show you what happens under the hood
告诉你幕后发生的事情
and basically based on this to draw some
并以此为基础
draw some conclusions when can you make
何时可以得出一些结论
your applications run faster when not
您的应用程序在不运行时运行得更快
I'm a software engineer at CERN for the
我是CERN的软件工程师
last nine years and okay so CERN what is
过去九年了，好的，CERN是什么
it it's a in a nutshell it's a word
简而言之，这是一个词
largest Physics Laboratory so basically
基本上是最大的物理实验室
we study the like the building blocks of
我们研究像
nature and we'll try to answer like
大自然，我们将尝试像
serious questions like what when was the
严重的问题，例如什么时候
university that what are the origins of
大学是什么起源的
it and so on and in the physics it's
等等，在物理学上
kind of funny because for the smaller
有点有趣，因为对于较小的
you look with the bigger you need so how
你看你需要更大的东西，怎么
do we do it
我们会做吗
well by building and maintaining
通过建立和维护很好
operating huge particle accelerators and
运行巨大的粒子加速器和
maybe one of those you know is the Large
也许您知道的其中一个是大型
Hadron Collider that biggest machine
强子对撞机最大的机器
ever built by a man it's like 17 miles
曾经由一个人建造过，就像17英里
right 17 miles long
对17英里长
300 meters below the ground and yeah so
地下300米，是的
it's really placed between French and
它真的放在法国和
Swiss border a bit further in the
瑞士边境在
background you will find a beautiful
背景你会发现一个美丽的
beautiful Alps in the best skiing
最好的滑雪美丽的阿尔卑斯山
resorts in Europe so the key elements in
在欧洲度假，所以其中的关键要素
the map and of course by doing this kind
地图，当然也可以这样做
of things by pushing the frontiers of of
通过推动的前沿
knowledge at some times there are very
有时知识非常
nice spin-offs created so maybe well
创造了很好的分拆，所以也许很好
CERN is also the place where the web was
欧洲核子研究组织也是网络的所在地
born you probably heard about it it was
天生的你可能听说过
invented by Tim berners-lee in 89 if I
蒂姆·伯纳斯·李（Tim berners-lee）在89年发明的
if I'm not mistaken so this is the like
如果我没记错的话，就像
the work first web server ever
有史以来第一台工作的Web服务器
and obviously the gentleman wasn't very
显然这位先生不是很
fond of switching it off because well by
喜欢关闭它，因为
switching it off you would switch the
关闭它，您将切换
whole web of so on not the not the best
这样的整个网络不是最好的
idea but okay as much as I would like to
这个主意，但我愿意
talk more about that soon we can have a
谈论更多关于我们可以很快
chat afterwards
之后聊天
let's not let's not keep our CPUs little
我们不要让我们的CPU少一点
so let's go let's go straight to the
所以我们走吧，我们直接去
business you don't really you don't need
您实际上不需要的业务
to follow what the code does it's just
遵循代码的作用
something to start with so I think that
首先要开始，所以我认为
every one of you would agree that
你们每个人都同意
collections are one of the most heaviest
收藏是最重的收藏之一
api's in Java but actually despite being
api是Java的，但实际上尽管
necessary for almost every job
几乎所有工作都需要
application manipulating them it's
操纵它们的应用程序
always kind of painful so whenever you
总是有点痛苦，所以每当你
have to do something you always get like
必须做一些你总是喜欢的事情
a fine point that man why I'm actually
那个男人为什么我实际上很好
struggling again with this so you know
再次为此挣扎，所以你知道
you know yourself best how many times
你最了解自己多少次
did you find yourself free implementing
您是否发现自己可以自由实施
over and over the same database like
遍历相同的数据库
operations using all these control
使用所有这些控件的操作
blocks like all the slopes ifs and so on
像所有斜坡一样的块ifs等等
and this is exactly what stream API is
而这正是流API
trying to address so basically here on
试图在这里基本上解决
the slide you have the exactly the same
幻灯片完全一样
functionality and it's nice it really
功能，真的很好
reads like a problem statement statement
读起来像问题陈述
and this is actually exactly what
这实际上就是
streams are about so they are an update
流是关于，所以他们是一个更新
to java api that simply let you
到让您轻松使用的Java API
manipulate collections well not only
不仅善于操作收藏
collections are actually like a sequence
集合实际上就像一个序列
set of values in a declarative way so
以声明的方式设置一组值
you say you say what you want instead of
你说你说你想要什么而不是
actually how really to do it if you if
实际上，如果您
you look for a metaphor it's like when
你寻找一个比喻，就像什么时候
you when you watch a movie over the
您在看电影时
internet it's like a stream so that the
互联网就像流一样，
frames the elements of the stream keep
框架流保持的元素
flowing if you have like a movie on on a
如果你喜欢在电影上
DVD it'll be more like a collection if
DVD如果更像是收藏
you if you interval Asif II a stream
你如果你间隔Asif II流
would be like a set of values spread
就像一组传播的价值观
over time and whereas a collection would
随着时间的流逝，而一个收集会
be like maybe set a value spread over
就像设置一个值
space
空间
well computer space in our case one more
在我们的情况下，计算机空间又多了
example with the with the stream well
流很好的例子
what we do here we have a bunch of bunch
我们在这里做什么我们有一堆
of numbers we map them which will filter
我们将它们映射的数量进行过滤
only those that are primes then we check
只有那些素数，然后我们检查
we convert them to the binary string
我们将它们转换为二进制字符串
then we check whether it's a palindrome
然后我们检查是否是回文
so whether if you read it from left to
因此，是否从左至右阅读
the right or from right to the left it
左右或从右到左
will be the same and we count our
将是相同的，我们算我们的
how many we have of those and actually
我们有几个，实际上
although this probably this example
虽然这可能是这个例子
doesn't make sense at all
完全没有道理
still you need like you need like five
仍然需要像五个一样
seconds to figure it out what it exactly
几秒钟就能弄清楚它到底是什么
does and this is exactly what the what
确实，这正是什么
the streams are about but what about
溪流是关于但那怎么办
what about its performance so like is
它的性能怎么样
prime calculating prime numbers it's
素数计算素数
kind of a difficult task well it has to
好困难的事情，它必须
be difficult because otherwise all the
很难，因为否则
symmetric cryptography would break so
对称密码学会因此中断
it's kind of CPOE first e and if you
这是CPOE first e，如果您
think about the progress in the in the
考虑一下
chip making so when you look at when you
芯片制造，所以当你看着你
look back so how did the characteristics
回头看，特性如何
of the main sleep chips changed over the
主要睡眠芯片的变化
years so for like I don't know two three
年，因为我不知道二三
decades we had a very nice times but
几十年来，我们度过了一段美好的时光，
basically everywhere every year we had
基本上每年我们都有
this exponential row growth and in the
这个指数行增长和
clock speed so basically all you had to
时钟速度，所以基本上您只需要
do to make this application faster is to
使此应用程序更快的方法是
go to the is to go to the store buy a
去的就是去商店买一个
new PC every year or every 18 months and
每年或每18个月购买一台新PC，
voila it was twice as fast and well the
瞧，速度快了两倍
life was that was that good
生活就是那样美好
till like 2000 something when they were
直到2000年左右
when the Moore's Law on it could give
当摩尔定律可以给出
you actually were not really faster
你实际上并不快
course but more cores so in order
当然要有更多核心
actually to speed up to speed up the
实际上要加快
application really had to leverage the
应用程序确实必须利用
multi-core architectures and I think in
多核架构，我认为
Java is particularly nice to see how
Java特别好看
they have the hardware trends were
他们的硬件趋势是
really shaping that the software trend
真正塑造了软件趋势
so if you think about when you go again
所以如果你想什么时候再去
a bit back in time sorta so from the
有点时光倒流，所以从
very early days you had the frets API it
在很早的时候，您就拥有了frets API
was well what what it does it basically
很好，它基本上是做什么的
Forks off from the main execution line
从主执行线分叉
and you can simply execute some stuff in
你可以简单地执行一些东西
the background
的背景
it wasn't about multi-core at this time
这不是关于多核的
well beginning and end of 90s it was
90年代的开始和结束
more more of to make your UI not
更多的使您的用户界面不
responsive and so on and I think that's
响应性等等，我认为那是
also the message in the presentation is
演示文稿中的消息是
that the good ol Fred it's still good
好的弗雷德，仍然很好
for a certain tasks if you have
对于某些任务，如果您有
something very very little you would
你会很少的东西
like to do in the background well go you
喜欢在后台做你
see it can go for a fret because if you
看到它会烦恼，因为如果你
apply the parallel streams everywhere
在所有地方应用并行流
well you were very simply a very quickly
好吧，你只是非常快
make a conclusion that Java 8 completely
结论是Java 8完全
sucks and it definitely doesn't you it
很烂，绝对不是你
just that the parallel streams they have
只是他们拥有的平行流
this discrete responsibility to handle
这种分立的责任
CPU hungry tasks if we go if we move a
如果我们移动一个CPU饥饿的任务
bit forward in time while JDK was JDK 5
在JDK是JDK 5的时候有点向前
was quite generous we went because when
我们很慷慨，因为
the multi-core CPUs were becoming more
多核CPU越来越多
popular so you had you had concurrent
受欢迎，所以你有并发
collections you had the semaphores you
收集了您的信号量
had the blocking queues you also had an
有阻塞队列，你也有一个
executor service and the fretful thread
执行程序服务和烦人的线程
pools I just listed it here because we
池我刚刚在这里列出，因为我们
know we're gonna reference and back to
知道我们会参考并返回
it so the idea of the executor service
所以执行者服务的想法
well is very simple you have just like a
嗯，很简单，你就像
container a bunch of threads it's just
容器只是一堆线程
the guys that are waiting for your work
那些等你工作的人
so you just submit the work there and it
所以你只提交那里的工作
will be done for you so it's really it's
会为您完成的，所以确实是
gonna take care of of this creation of
要照顾这个创造
the creation management and execution of
创建管理和执行
the threat and you can you can have
威胁，你可以拥有
different variations of the of the
的不同变化
executor service and the fretful so for
遗嘱执行人服务和烦躁的
example you can have that with a fixed
例如，您可以将其固定
number of threads you can have the
您可以拥有的线程数
scheduled one that basically consents
预定一个基本同意的
something and say hey execute this thing
东西说嘿执行这个东西
in half an hour or execute it
在半小时内或执行它
periodically every five minutes so it
每五分钟定期进行一次
was very nice addition all that to the
很不错的补充
api okay if we move forward in the again
api好的，如果我们再次前进
forward in time we land with the will
随着时间的流逝，我们会按照意愿着陆
will land with the with the parallel
将与平行降落
streams so which is on the previous
流，因此在前一个
slide this nice and sweet declarative
滑动这个漂亮而甜美的声明
syntax to process your your data your
处理您的数据的语法
collections it's just one of the goodies
收藏只是好东西之一
that the streams are about so what they
这些流是关于它们的
what they also let you to do so on top
他们还让您做到了什么
of that you can execute those those
你可以执行那些
streams almost for free on your on your
几乎免费为您串流
core CPUs so basically all you have to
核心CPU，所以基本上您只需要
do is to turn your swim into a parallel
要做的就是将游泳变成平行运动
stream so as you can see on this light
流，如您所见
on that well is the code visible in the
在那口井上的代码是可见的
in the back I'm not sure what what what
在后面我不确定什么
I do if it wasn't but well probably it's
如果不是，我会这样做，但很可能是
polite to ask as well so basically on
基本上也要礼貌地问
the on the on the left side we have
在左侧
again our nonsensical prime number
再次是我们荒谬的素数
palindromic example if it's if the
回文示例，如果
streams rice runs sequentially it takes
溪流按顺序运行
like a bit less than nine seconds to
大概不到九秒
execute if I just make it if I just
如果我做到就执行
indicate that this should be executed in
指示应在以下位置执行
parallel it's gonna take well it's it's
平行它会很好的是
up by the factor five so how is how is
上升了五倍，怎么回事
this possible what is what is what is
这可能是什么是什么
the trick well the main trick is that
这个技巧很好，主要的技巧是
with Java streams API it employs the
使用Java Streams API时，
internal iteration again if we think
如果我们认为内部迭代又一次
about the metaphor when my fiancee tells
关于未婚妻告诉我的隐喻
me to was to wash the dishes she can she
我要去洗碗她可以
can do it she can apply the external
可以做到，她可以申请外部
iteration so she can tell me was the
迭代，所以她可以告诉我是
fork was the knife was the plate or she
叉子是刀子还是盘子
can really if she has that trust in me
真的可以，只要她对我有信任
she can say just wash the dishes and
她可以说洗碗
it's gonna be who who is going to pick
将会是谁来选择
up the plates the knives and maybe I can
把盘子放到刀子上，也许我可以
introduce some optimizations so this is
引入一些优化，所以这是
like the main basically the main trick
喜欢主要的主要技巧
it does and interval and in the
它确实和间隔，并在
background it employs this fork/join
它使用此fork / join的背景
framework and the splitter writer and
框架和分割器作者，以及
this is exactly what we gonna see in in
这正是我们将要看到的
detail but before that I told you about
细节，但在此之前我告诉过您
turning a stream into a parallel one so
将流变成并行的流
what does it what does it really mean
这到底是什么意思
how do you do it so we basically have
你如何做到的，所以我们基本上有
two options the first is if the stream
两个选择第一个是如果流
source we say is a collection basically
我们所说的来源基本上是一个集合
all you have to do is to just evoke the
您要做的就是唤起
parallel swim method on your source if
如果您的源上并行游泳方法
it's like a generator function or
这就像一个生成器函数或
something else but it still can be
其他的东西，但仍然可以
actually a collection you can always you
实际上，您可以随时收藏
have this in your stream pipeline you
在您的流管道中拥有这个
have this parallel
有这个平行
method and it doesn't really matter
方法并不重要
doesn't it doesn't really matter where
是不是真的在哪里都没关系
this method is actually how
这种方法实际上是
we're in your pipeline it is placed so
我们在您的管道中，因此放置
whether you place it like Indy in the
是否将其像印地一样放在
end or you place it in the middle it
结束或您将其放在中间
does not really matter why because when
并不重要，为什么，因为何时
you think about the anatomy of the of
您考虑的解​​剖
the of the stream all those operation
所有这些操作的流
except the last one are those
除了最后一个是那些
intermediate operations so is it it's
中间操作，就是这样
very much like the Builder pattern so
非常类似于Builder模式
you just keep saying stuff that what you
你只是一直说些什么
want to do but nothing is gonna really
想做，但什么都不会真的
happen till the terminal operation it's
发生直到终端操作
gonna be invoked so really the terminal
真的会被终端调用
operation is the boss so it's really the
操作是老板，所以实际上
thing is not gonna do anything until we
直到我们做任何事情
invoke the terminal operation okay so I
调用终端操作好吧，所以我
said before that we have this focus on
之前说过，我们专注于
framework which is the heart of the
框架是核心
parallel swimming this is what is being
平行游泳这是什么
done this is what is being employed in
做到这一点是在雇用
the background and let's have a look at
背景，让我们来看看
it it was when I did a little time
那是我做了一点时间的时候
travel before I was a bit I skipped it
在我稍稍走过去之前旅行
over deliberately so this was added in a
故意超过，所以这被添加到一个
JDK five and yeah but it's maybe it
JDK 5，是的，但也许是
wasn't that famous bit is it because
那不是很有名吗，因为
it's a kind of low-level and I think
这是一种低水平的，我认为
it's a bit of overstatement to call it a
夸大其词有点夸张
framework but yeah it wasn't really me
框架，但不是我
doing it all right so what is a
没事做，那是什么
fork/join framework it's also
fork / join框架也是
implementation of the executor service
执行服务的实施
so it's really nothing more than the
所以实际上只不过是
again then the thread pool with a bunch
再然后是一堆线程池
of threads that you just sent your you
您刚发送给您的线程数
just send that it's that can you that
只是发送那是你可以的
that lets you execute our code in in
使您可以在
parallel so the major difference however
平行，所以主要区别
comparing to the executor service we saw
与我们看到的执行者服务相比
a few slides a few slides ago he saw is
他看到的几张幻灯片
that it was designed to for a CPU hungry
专为CPU饥饿而设计
tasks so it was really designed to to
任务，所以它真的旨在
recursively split well fork process and
递归拆分井分叉过程和
finally join and the results so
最终加入，结果如此
if we think about if you think about an
如果我们考虑如果您考虑
example how does it how does it work so
示例它是如何工作的
imagine this can be an array of number
想象这可以是数字数组
and all we want to do we would like to
我们想做的所有事情
add those numbers and as we have a lot
加上这些数字，因为我们有很多
of the of those numbers we would like to
这些数字中，我们希望
do it in parallel so basically what
并行执行，基本上
you're doing it's just the famous divide
你正在做的只是著名的鸿沟
and conquer you just skip you just
征服你只是跳过你而已
partition the array till it will be
分割阵列，直到将
small enough that you will conclude okay
足够小，您将得出结论
actually it's not worth any more to
其实不值得了
executed to paralyze it further further
被执行以使其进一步瘫痪
I do it sequentially and then this is
我依次执行，然后是
where the steps jumps in and then of
步骤跳到哪里，然后
course you did you did the divided step
当然你做了分步
now we need to conquer it you simply
现在我们只需征服你
join those tasks to carry on with the
加入这些任务以继续
with this example it's I think it's not
这个例子是我认为不是
even crucial really Toto follow all the
甚至至关重要的Toto都遵循所有
code it's more again about the idea how
编码，这再次是关于如何
it how it works
它如何运作
so as I said we have a Fortran framework
正如我所说的，我们有一个Fortran框架
which is a key implementation a graph of
这是一个关键的实现图
the executor service so we must send it
执行者服务，所以我们必须发送它
we must send it a task please please do
我们必须发送任务给我
it and of course so first we must
它，当然首先，我们必须
implement the task so basically your you
完成任务，基本上就是你
always should you can you must implement
总是应该可以实施
it must be there the incident ask must
它必须在那里发生事件询问必须
be the instance of the recursive task or
是递归任务的实例，或者
every recursive action the difference is
每个递归操作的区别是
if it recursive task it returns a result
如果是递归任务，则返回结果
if it's not a recursive if it's a
如果不是递归的话
recursive action it doesn't return the
递归操作不会返回
result so it's like a consumer it just
结果，就像消费者一样
does something but it doesn't do
做某事但没有做
anything I think on the Oracle website
我在Oracle网站上看到的任何内容
when you want to have the article about
当您想发表有关
parallel streams they have a very nice
并行流他们有一个非常好的
example that they basically they have a
例如，他们基本上有一个
array of some numbers of like a picture
像图片一样的一些数字的数组
and they blur the picture and this would
他们模糊了图片，这会
be like a recursive action because you
像递归动作，因为你
just we don't return anything you just
只是我们不退还任何东西而已
process and they array okay but in our
过程，他们排列还可以，但是在我们的
case with the with the numbers we would
与数字的情况下，我们会
like to sum them up so there is only one
喜欢总结一下，所以只有一个
method that we need to implement which
我们需要实现的方法
is which is implement overwrite that we
是我们覆盖的工具
need to overwrite is the compute method
需要覆盖的是计算方法
and it's a kind of a simple approach so
这是一种简单的方法
first we see what is the
首先我们看什么是
of our task and then we have this well
完成我们的任务，然后我们就拥有了
the choice to make if it's small enough
如果足够小则选择
okay I don't bother dividing it further
好吧，我不会再将其分开
however if it's still big big enough so
但是如果它还足够大的话
it's worth - Voltorb to paralyze it I
值得-沃尔托布使我瘫痪
just do it so basically we just created
这样做，所以基本上我们刚刚创建了
the same two tasks we passed the same
我们通过相同的两个任务
numbers
数字
however the left and the left tasks will
但是，左边和左边的任务将
have well the left half of the array the
拥有阵列的左半部分
right task the right half of the array
正确的任务，数组的右半部分
and we simply execute it we forked so on
然后我们简单地执行它
our left task which we call the formal
我们的左手任务，我们称之为正式任务
method meaning call this call this a
方法的意思叫这个叫这个
synchronously and on our right task we
与我们同步执行正确的任务
can either call the fourth method again
可以再次调用第四个方法
but actually as we are already in the
但实际上就像我们已经在
India fret we know we do not need to do
印度担心，我们知道我们不需要做
any more for the time being with it we
暂时没有了，我们
can also compute it synchronously and
也可以同步计算
then we then we wait when two of them
然后我们等待，当他们两个
are we done and combined the result
我们完成并合并结果了吗
again it's not so crucial really to
同样，它对
understand understand it it's just just
了解了解这只是
the idea so we have our we have our
这个想法，所以我们有我们我们有我们的
tasks so right now we need to submit it
任务，所以现在我们需要提交它
somewhere and this is their witnesses
某个地方，这是他们的证人
and this is the fork/join and this is
这是分叉/联接，这是
the fork/join pool and okay so what do
叉子/联接池，好吧，该怎么办
we do here so we instantiate our our
我们在这里做，所以我们实例化我们的
some method we create the instance of
我们创建的实例的一些方法
the fork/join pool and this is kind of
叉子/联接池，这是一种
already crucial for the parallel streams
对于并行流已经至关重要
so you have two options so either you
所以你有两个选择
create a forging pull on your on your
在您的身上制造锻造拉力
own your Stan she ate it with a
拥有你的斯坦，她吃了一个
constructor you supply how many how many
您提供多少个构造函数
frets how many those guys that will be
担心会有多少人
doing that job for you should be should
为你做这份工作应该是
be there or you can use the common full
在那里，或者您可以使用普通饱餐
instance it's like very much like a like
实例非常像
a like a single tone so and what is
像是一个单音，那又是什么
characteristic for the parallel streams
并行流的特性
is that they always use the same common
是他们总是使用相同的共同点
pole instance so they really they always
极点实例，所以他们实际上他们总是
are all the time doesn't matter how many
一直都无所谓
parallel streams you have running how
您运行的并行流如何
many of them
许多人
running in the background they always
他们总是在后台运行
use the same thread pool you might you
使用与您可能相同的线程池
might actually ask yourself okay like
可能会问自己好吗
what the heck would default join
默认会加入什么
framework because basically we did all
框架，因为基本上我们都做了
the job on our own yes it is a kind of
我们自己的工作是一种
low a low level thing however it has few
低水平的东西，但是很少
characteristics that are a crucial
至关重要的特征
crucial also for the parallel streams so
对于并行流也至关重要
first as you saw before we have this
首先是您看到的，然后才有了这个
fork and join a method that we can
分叉并加入一种我们可以
nicely well fork off and and join it and
很好地分叉并加入
it all supplies this and this actually
这一切都提供了这个，实际上
like the brill the main characteristics
像毛坯一样的主要特点
and the fork join pool applies their
和fork join pool应用他们的
work still in calgary so basically in
仍然在卡尔加里工作，所以基本上
your fork giant pool you have like a
你的叉子巨池，你就像
bunch of frets how many we will see in
一堆的烦恼我们会看到多少
in a moment
一会儿
and those guys well they eat each each
那些家伙好，他们每个人都吃
guy each fred has a queue of tasks it
每个弗雷德的家伙都有一个任务队列
has to execute and if if a certain Fred
必须执行，如果某个弗雷德
run run runs out of the tasks well it is
运行运行可以很好地完成任务
greedy so it's simply looking for other
贪婪，所以它只是在寻找其他
in other threads excuse if there is
在其他线程里找借口
something to do and this kind of if you
要做的事情，如果你
were wondering like in the previous
在想像以前
example what happened if my left or
例如，如果我的左手或
right task would be finished before day
正确的任务将在一天之前完成
before the other well it's not a big
在另一口井之前不是很大
deal because if it will be finished way
处理，因为如果将完成的方式
before and will be bored well it's not
以前会很无聊，不是
going to be it's gonna still the tasks
将会是仍然的任务
for from other Fred okay again all the
从其他弗雷德好吧再次所有
parallel streams they usually a one and
并行流通常是一个
the same common pull instance you might
您可能会使用的相同的普通提取实例
wonder okay how many frets we we have
想知道我们有多少个品格
there the number of it the the number
那里的数字
it's a number of your CPUs minus one
这是您的CPU数减去一
okay why actually -1 why what what
好吧，为什么实际上-1为什么是什么
happened to the other two the last two
最后两个发生在另外两个
the last call on the last CA oh and the
最后一个CA上的最后一个电话
thing is that this is the how the
事实是，这就是
library is designed that also the the
库的设计还
fret that invokes that invokes the
调用的品格
submits the task to the for example it's
提交任务到例如
also becoming a worker so that the end
也成为工人，以便最终
it's this minus one plus one
这是一减一
so technically effectively you have the
从技术上讲，您拥有
number your common pool is gonna work
号码，你的公共游泳池会工作
with as many threads as you have CPUs in
与您拥有的CPU一样多的线程
your new PC if you would like change
如果您想更换新电脑
those well you can use this property to
那些很好，您可以使用此属性
to set it but again if you think about
进行设置，但是如果您考虑过
it that the parallel streams they should
他们应该并行流
be executed well they should really take
被很好地执行，他们应该真正采取
care of the CPU hungry tasks I'm not
照顾我不是CPU饥饿的任务
really sure if it makes make sense
真的确定这是否有意义
because if you if you create more than
因为如果您创建的内容超过
you have CPUs well it just would be like
你有很好的CPU，就像
a certain cost dozen overhead also as it
一定的成本也打了一些开销
as the common pool it's a kind of a
作为公共游泳池，这是一种
single ton of course when you do it you
当然，当您这样做时，
must always do it before you actually
在您实际操作之前必须始终这样做
invoke your first parallel stream so you
调用您的第一个并行流，这样您
cannot find granulated okay let's
找不到颗粒好吧，让我们
execute this parallel stream with two
用两个执行此并行流
cores change this parameter to eight
核心将此参数更改为八个
let's execute it with eight cores and so
让我们以八个核心执行它
on no it doesn't work this way
不，这是行不通的
once you invoke your very first parallel
一旦您调用了第一个并行
stream this this won't be considered any
流这不会被认为是任何
more so probably you should pass it like
更可能是您应该通过它
on the on the comment line okay so I've
在评论行上，好，我已经
been I kept repeating for like five
我一直重复五次
hundred times that parallel streams they
他们并行流的一百倍
always use the same instance of the of
始终使用的相同实例
the fork/join pool the question is can
问题是可以的fork / join pool
you use your can you use your own so can
您可以使用您可以使用的您自己的可以
you say okay this parallel stream should
你说好，这个并行流应该
include this should be executed really
包括这应该真的执行
with this one and only for example the
与此有关，例如
answer is yes however I I just show it
答案是可以的，但是我只是显示一下
for the completeness sake because it's
为了完整起见，因为
something I wouldn't I wouldn't really
我不会，我不会真的
do so how do you do it well if you look
这样做，如果你看起来很好
at the fork method what it exactly does
在fork方法中它的确切作用
this guy is a kind of context-sensitive
这个家伙是上下文相关的一种
so that if it's running if it's already
这样就可以知道它是否正在运行
running in a certain pool it just gonna
在某个游泳池里跑，它只会
is just gonna stick to there so
只会坚持在那里
basically the trick is to to create your
基本上，诀窍是创建您的
fork joint pool with as many threads as
叉接头池的线程数与
you want and then simply submit submit
您想要然后提交
your parallel stream execution and there
您的并行流执行以及
and again Shawn for completeness sake
为了完整起见，肖恩又一次
it's not something about I would what I
这与我的意愿无关
would really do you're probably can have
你可能真的会拥有
well if you look for a reasons to do it
好，如果您寻找这样做的理由
well I'm against it but I'm trying to be
好吧，我反对，但我想成为
as objective as possible like a kind of
尽可能客观地
a lawyer or something so if you think
律师之类的话，如果您认为
why should you do it
你为什么要这样做
well first you don't have well of course
首先，你当然身体不好
you have a you have a separate pool
你有一个你有一个单独的游泳池
you're not gonna in your common pool
你不会在普通的游泳池
it's not going to be affected by it
它不会受到它的影响
maybe if you had like a case is that
也许如果您有个案例是
because of this threat sharing you know
因为这种威胁共享，你知道
that the threat that calls it it's also
所谓的威胁也是
involved to you who you would have like
想要你参与
a threats of a different life cycles I
不同生命周期的威胁
could potentially imagine some problems
可能会想到一些问题
with that with the transactions and so
与交易等
on the second reason is that if you
第二个原因是，如果您
invoke the parallel stream and one of
调用并行流和以下之一
the threads get gets stuck what it gets
线程被卡住了
taxed it gets it gets stuck forever so
征税它永远卡住，所以
this is something watch what you can
这是你可以看的东西
influence in this case because well you
影响在这种情况下，因为你好
can really define a time out a parallel
可以真正定义一个平行的超时
stream please do it for me but actually
流请帮我做，但实际上
wait only max ten seconds so again this
最多只等待十秒钟，所以再次
is like the reasons that could be a
就像原因可能是
reason actually to to go for it okay if
真正去做的理由好吧，如果
we try to draw some conclusions from
我们试图从中得出一些结论
from the fork fork/join framework again
再次从fork fork / join框架
nothing more than a just like a
无非就是一个像
recursive divide and conquer algorithm
递归分治法
so as we have one short pull with not so
所以我们有一个短暂的拉力
many threads or basically as many
很多线程或基本上一样多
threads as you have a CPU scores of the
CPU得分为
virtual course is avoid IO because of
虚拟过程是避免IO，因为
course every every time you wait for
每次您等待时当然
something bit like a disk or network
有点像磁盘或网络
resource you're gonna burn all these CPU
资源将消耗所有这些CPU
cycles again used for intensive CPU CPU
周期再次用于密集型CPU
intensive tasks so when you're when you
繁重的任务，所以当您在
stick to it then all the common pool all
坚持下去，然后所有公共池
the defaults they were really perfectly
默认值是非常完美的
perfectly and make sense mind if you
完美，如果你有头脑的话
have like parallel streams because well
之所以喜欢并行流，是因为
if you have like a parallel stream
如果您喜欢并行流
having maybe like a for each and in the
也许每个人都有一个
for each you have another power per
对于每一个你有另一个力量
other stream because then you can look
其他流，因为这样你可以看
and then you can might have some
然后你可能会有一些
anomalies we can clearly have a chat
我们可以很明显地聊天
about it later I did some tests I there
后来我在那里做了一些测试
is no not really enough time to show it
并不是没有足够的时间来展示它
but yeah you can you can you can
但是，是的，你可以，你可以
actually find out yourself that I think
真正发现自己，我认为
will will be pretty slow and because of
将会很慢，因为
the worker pull so they were the key why
工人拉，所以他们是关键
the for join framework actually exists
for连接框架实际上存在
always prefer to have more more tasks
总是喜欢有更多的任务
and then necessary because if you think
然后有必要，因为如果您认为
if you have 128 course but you have like
如果您有128门课程，但是您喜欢
mega 80 of mega tasks well you can only
兆丰80兆丰的任务，你只能
use like I don't know your CPU for 60 70
使用就像我不知道你的CPU 60 70
percent I mean the power you you have
我是说你拥有的力量
and again rather stick to the common
再一次坚持普通
apple because it just it just makes
苹果，因为它只是使
sense okay so this is the fork/join
感觉还可以，所以这是fork / join
framework and right now in the example
框架，现在在示例中
when we were adding the numbers you saw
当我们加上您看到的数字时
that we kind nice and evenly splitted
我们友善，平分秋色
our array of numbers in the left and and
我们左边的数字数组和
the right part
正确的部分
but as you know stream can have many
但是如您所知，流可以有很多
many sources actually you can also
实际上，许多来源也可以
create your own streams so some
创建自己的流，所以一些
sometimes we need a way to to influence
有时我们需要一种方法来影响
how this thing is how this thing is
这东西怎么样这东西怎么样
actual annoying and get split so when we
实际的烦人和分裂，所以当我们
are in this fork part well we need
在这个叉子部分，我们需要
somehow instructed or it somehow must be
以某种方式指示或必须以某种方式
smart enough to instruct itself how this
足够聪明地指示自己如何
thing should be splitted and this is
东西应该分开，这是
something what was introduced in a new
新东西中引入的一些东西
interface that was introduced in Java 8
Java 8中引入的接口
which is a splitter writer which is
这是一个分裂作家，
split table iterator it even stands here
拆分表迭代器，它甚至可以站在这里
ok
好
and it's basically designed designed to
它基本上是设计用来
go through your elements in parallel so
并行浏览您的元素，以便
yeah to kind of apply the iterator
是的，可以应用迭代器
in whatever number of course you have so
无论你有多少，
how how does it work
如何运作
it has well it has actually a bunch of
它的确有很多
methods but those are the main free ones
方法，但那些是主要的免费方法
so as you know the classic iterator it
如您所知，经典的迭代器
has this has past next and next so
有这个过去和下一个过去了吗
simply if do I have something do I still
只是如果我有什么我仍然
have something and if yes please give it
有东西，如果是，请给
to me
对我来说
the try advanced it's kind of
尝试先进的那种
incorporation of those two methods so it
合并这两种方法
returns a boolean telling you whether it
返回一个布尔值，告诉您是否
there is still something in the in the
里面还有东西
in your splitter writer but it also
在您的拆分器作家中
takes a consumer that simply does
拿一个简单地做的消费者
something with your with your element
与您的元素有关
that it was currently iterating through
目前正在迭代
and it when you think about it it's
当你考虑它的时候
really nicely pep makes sense how does
真的很好，激励是有道理的
how everything connects together because
一切如何联系在一起，因为
when you work with your streams you
当您使用流时，您会
nicely past you can use the lambdas to
过去，您可以使用Lambda
pass to pass the behavior and again if
通过传递行为，如果
you have a consumers and so on derive
你有一个消费者，等等
originally passed there another method
最初通过那里另一种方法
which is like the heart of the split
就像分裂的心脏
aerator is the Tri split so it does two
曝气机是Tri分裂的，所以它做两个
things
东西
it returns a new splitter writer and
它返回一个新的拆分器作家，
it's changing the coverage of the
它正在改变
current one we also have the
目前我们也有
characteristics when you speed it just
加快速度时的特性
like some hints to environment to speed
像环境加速的一些提示
up to introduce some optimistic
来介绍一些乐观的看法
optimizations and so on so let's see
优化等等，让我们来看看
that try split in action little because
尝试分裂行动的原因很少
again it has some consequences how you
再次有一些后果，你如何
can what should you think about when you
请问您什么时候可以考虑
think about the performance of your
考虑一下你的表现
parallel stream so we have our splitter
并行流，所以我们有分离器
writer again beat beat again a huge
作家再次击败巨大
array of numbers so when we invoke the
数字数组，因此当我们调用
Tri split on this guy it does two things
Tri在这个家伙身上分裂了两件事
so first it's returning a new splitter
所以首先它要返回一个新的分离器
writer which would be like okay I don't
作家，那会很好，我不
know if the numbers are from one to
知道数字是否从一到
hundred it will terminate from 1 to 50
百，它将从1终止到50
but at the same time it's changing the
但同时它正在改变
coverage of the splitter writer so this
分离器作家的报道
would be from 1 to 50 this would be from
从1到50这将是从
51 to hundred so this is exactly
51至100
actually the the whole trick it does
实际上是整个技巧
you do it again and it does exactly the
你再做一次，它确实做了
same thing so on our on our splitter
同样的事情在我们的分离器上
rater one it returns a new splitter
评分者一返回新的拆分器
writer would be from 1 to 25 and it's
作家将是1到25，这是
changing the coverage of of these guys
改变这些家伙的报道
what would be from 26 to 50 so this is
从26到50是多少，所以这是
the whole and the whole trick how
整个和整个技巧
actually the parallel stream gets forked
实际上并行流被分叉了
and we do this thing over and over till
我们一遍又一遍地做这件事，直到
that till the Tri speed return channel
直到三速返回通道
and then we know okay we're done with
然后我们知道好了
the forking step now we can another
现在分叉的步骤，我们可以再
parallel stream can process this in
并行流可以在
sequentially and later join it so when
先后顺序加入，所以当
you look at the splitter rater one it's
你看一个分流器是
really this guy it's all the time the
真的这个家伙一直在
same object it just with the it got to
同一个对象
times
次
tri-split invoked on it so it's coverage
三重分割调用它，所以它的覆盖范围
was shrinking the question is can you
在缩小问题是
use your own splitter rater for a stream
使用自己的分离器评分器进行流
you can so you have the stream support
您可以这样就可以得到流支持
class it's like a low-level class that
类就像一个低级的类
you can construct as streams and yeah so
您可以构建为流，是的，所以
basically you have this stream method
基本上你有这个流方法
that you pass your your splitter writer
您通过了拆分器作者
I'm not sure if you ever really going
我不确定你是否真的去过
you need to need to do it again it's
您需要再次做一次
good to understand how this thing is
很高兴了解这件事是怎么回事
working under the hood maybe if you have
在幕后工作，如果你有
like a enumeration I'm not sure if you
像枚举，我不确定你是否
can create an enumeration out if you can
可以创建一个枚举
create a stream out of the enumeration
通过枚举创建流
what we might be like one of the cases
我们可能会是其中一种情况
if you were writing your new collection
如果您正在编写新收藏
and you're not very fond of the default
而且您不太喜欢默认值
implementation of the Tri speed would be
三速的实施将是
one also like the case or simply if the
一个也喜欢这种情况或简单地
elements in your streams they have
流中的元素
certain semantics that the default
某些默认的语义
default splitting process wouldn't make
默认的拆分过程不会
sense for you then you can influence the
对你而言，那么你就可以影响
process but again probably you're not
过程，但再次可能你不是
really going to need it
真的需要它
okay so when we again stick to the to
好的，所以当我们再次坚持到
the to display splitter writer so
显示拆分器的作者
basically imagine we have a we have a
基本上想象我们有一个
linked list
链表
we call a we call a splitter rater on it
我们称其为分离器评分器
well it returns a linked list splitter
好吧，它返回一个链接列表拆分器
writer of course of a type what are my
我当然是作家
elements in the list and right now what
列表中的元素，现在
we do first on our splitter writer the
我们首先对我们的分离器作家进行
many ones are really the one on on top
许多真的是最重要的一个
it has 10 K 10 K elements if we try
如果我们尝试，它有10 K 10 K个元素
split again it does it does two things
再次拆分，它做两件事
is it it returns a new one so this is
它是否返回一个新的，所以这是
the one is being returned so it's size
一个被退回，所以它的大小
is like 1k so you can see it on the
就像1k，所以您可以在
picture and it's changing the coverage
图片，它正在改变覆盖范围
of its of of its of itself so basically
本身就这么基本
this is what hey what happened and if we
这就是发生了什么，如果我们
do the exactly the same thing for a for
为做完全相同的事情
a for an arraylist well we have a
对于数组列表，我们有一个
realistic splitter writer where we see
现实的分裂作家，我们看到的
what is his size we call it
他叫什么尺寸
tri-split and then we see what is the
三分，然后我们看什么是
size of the of the new one and all the
新的和所有的大小
wonder that coverage coverage got
想知道覆盖范围得到了
changed and if you look at the array
改变了，如果你看一下数组
list it's nicely and evenly divided
列出它均匀均匀地划分
however if you look at the if you look
但是如果你看着
at the linked list well it's like this
在链表上，就像这样
kind of mini mini list that was created
所创建的迷你迷你列表的种类
and why is it like this because well
为什么会这样，因为
whenever we start whenever we start a
每当我们开始每当我们开始
problem that we want execute in parallel
我们要并行执行的问题
we always start at one core I mean the
我们总是从一个核心开始
problem it's never multicolor from the
问题是它永远不会是多色的
from the from the from the start so one
从一开始就如此
actually we call this tri-split
实际上我们称之为三分
and you know in order to split a linked
而且您知道为了拆分链接
list you really have to have to go
列出你确实必须去的
through the elements so when we actually
通过元素，所以当我们实际上
doing it even if we have 500 course it's
即使我们有500门课程，
like 499 course that will be slipping
像499课程将滑倒
because it's only one core that will
因为这只是一个核心
it's invoking that right split so the
它正在调用该右拆分，因此
guy saw the guys at at Oracle they just
人在甲骨文看到他们
provided some intelligent
提供了一些聪明
implementations depending on the of the
实现取决于
data structure is like okay if I have a
如果我有一个数据结构就好了
linked list please I want to actually
链接列表，我想实际
fork as soon as
尽快叉
for cough as soon as possible so this is
尽快咳嗽，这是
actually the reason why this is not so
其实不是这样的原因
well not evenly divided and this of
以及没有平均分配和这个
course means that for a strategy for a
当然，对于一个
parallel stream certain sources are more
并行流某些来源更多
friendlier than the other so whenever
比其他人更友好
you have this when you create when you
当您创建时，您拥有此
create create the tree when you go from
当您离开时创建树
the root to the Leafs it kind of matters
枫叶的根源很重要
what what's your what you're doing so if
你在做什么，如果
we have a linked list
我们有一个链表
you already saw it again it's a knot you
你已经再次看到它是一个结你
need to walk through the guy iteratively
需要迭代地穿过那个家伙
so it can be expensive when you use the
因此，当您使用
generator function well it's a iterative
生成器函数很好，这是一个迭代
generator it has the same
具有相同的发电机
characteristics to to generate the
特征产生
elements as a as a linked list I've set
元素作为我设置的链接列表
a net reset but something like in the in
净重置，但类似
the middle is probably it won't be a oh
中间可能不是哦
oh and it would be like something all
哦，就像一切
logarithms and and of course I released
对数，当然我也发布了
all the stages generators they are fine
所有阶段的发电机都很好
so again like one of the lessons
就像上一课一样
whenever you have a whenever you create
每当您创建时
a stream parallel stream think about the
一个流并行的流思考
stream stream source few a few examples
流流源几个例子
so basically what we what we have here
所以基本上我们在这里拥有什么
we have like 1 billion elements ok let's
我们有10亿个元素好吧，让我们
be let's be bold why not all we would
让我们大胆一点，为什么不全部
like to do is to compute their computer
喜欢做的是计算他们的计算机
their sum so first with the we're not
他们的总和，所以首先我们不是
going parallel it's a nice sequential
并行执行是一个很好的顺序
like the execution we have like one
像我们一样的处决
second if we just all we do here if we
第二，如果我们只是我们在这里所做的一切，
just try to parallel in parallel right
只是尝试并行并行
this guy with the default with the
这个家伙的默认
default heap size when you start a JVM
启动JVM时的默认堆大小
it explodes it actually explodes when
它爆炸时，实际上爆炸时
you when you try to when you try to
你当你尝试当你尝试
invoke the try speed method on the on
在on上调用try speed方法
the on the supreme source or even more
最高来源甚至更多
generally speaking if you create a
一般来说，如果您创建一个
linked list with 1 billion elements we
有十亿个元素的链表
invoke a tries please try split-- on it
尝试尝试，请尝试拆分-
it explodes so yeah because
它爆炸了，是的，因为
again when you think about the overhead
再次考虑开销时
it's quite heavy if we go for a
如果我们去一个很重的地方
stateless generator function which is
无状态发电机功能是
friendly and you do it in sequentially
友好，您可以按顺序进行
it's taking like 600 milliseconds and
大概需要600毫秒
you might actually wonder okay like what
您可能实际上想知道好吗
the heck those two guys they should have
他们应该有的两个家伙
a kind of similar performance because
一种类似的表现，因为
they are off it's a sequential run so as
他们关闭，这是一个顺序运行，以便
I as I do it sequentially I mean the
我按顺序进行是指
range shouldn't give me any benefit well
范围不应该给我任何好处
it it does because the iterate method it
它这样做是因为它有迭代方法
returns boxed objects so you have like 1
返回装箱的对象，所以你像1
billion objects that you need to box and
需要装箱的十亿个对象和
hunt box
狩猎盒
so yeah this can this really basically
所以是的，这真的可以
improves the preview improves the
改善预览效果
performance by twice if you don't if you
如果不这样做，性能提高两倍
don't do it so even though it might be
即使这样做可能也不要这样做
like a bit confusing ok I have I have a
有点令人困惑，好吧，我有一个
long streams I have the relief
漫长的溪流让我松了一口气
specialized stream this is what I read
专业流这是我读的
on the Stack Overflow to do but still
在堆栈溢出上做，但仍然
the iterator function or regenerate box
迭代器功能或重新生成框
objects and the the the some expects
对象和一些期望
unboxed objects and you have like boxing
未装箱的物品，您喜欢装箱
and unboxing a very unnecessarily so
拆箱非常不必要
this is exactly what the wrench in this
这正是这个扳手
case has changed and right now if we
情况已经改变，如果我们现在
call if we call the parallel method on
如果我们在调用并行方法，则调用
it still we have like different thing
还是我们有不同的感觉
execute five times faster ok all right
执行速度快五倍好吗
so find any and unordered so well maybe
所以找到任何无序的也许
the example probably explains its best
这个例子可能解释了最好的
so imagine we have this kind of very
所以想像我们有这种非常
simplistic stream of six elements and
六个元素的简化流
all we do here we just pre we just print
我们在这里所做的一切只是在打印之前
the elements of it nothing more . and of
它的元素仅此而已。和的
course as as we executing in parallel
就像我们并行执行一样
that is as it does the as it does the
这就是它做的那样
tree whenever you execute it it's
只要执行它就可以
producing something else obviously if
如果产生其他明显的东西
you if if we remove the power parallel
如果我们取消并联电源
out of here it would be nice like 1 2 3
离开这里就像1 2 3
4 5 6 however if it's as it's a parallel
4 5 6但是，如果它是并行的
stream well you cannot really predict
流得很好，您无法真正预测
the
的
order and if you if you want like to
订购，如果您愿意的话
find a evoke defined first a method on
找到一个首先定义一个方法的调用
this dream well it will the API it's
这个梦想很好，它将是API
smart it will always if you if we invoke
聪明，如果我们调用，它将永远
a find first it will always return one
首先查找，它将始终返回一个
so it would really obey to what you want
所以它真的会服从你想要的
to what you want but this is an overhead
到您想要的东西，但这是开销
because when you think about it okay the
因为当你考虑好了
kind of natural order of this parallel
这种平行的自然顺序
stream it's random it is this so if I
流是随机的，所以如果我
tell this guy give me the first one he
告诉这个家伙给我第一个他
must he must do he must do some effort
他必须做他必须做些努力
okay what was actually on your first
好吧，实际上你的第一个
element so just prefer just preferred to
元素，所以只喜欢只喜欢
use if you not really worried if you'd
如果您真的不担心，请使用
not really don't care which one should
真的不在乎哪一个
it be we turn find any because find
轮到我们找到任何东西了，因为找到了
first would be like the one always one
首先就像永远是一个
but if you invoke a fine tiny little
但是如果您调用一个细小的
piddly AK four six two if you don't
如果你不喜欢的话，AK四四六二
really care about it go for it it will
真的很在乎它会
be faster at the same about a limit
在相同的极限下更快
method so if you invoke the limit free
方法，因此，如果您调用无限制
on this stream it will return like one
在这一流上，它会像一个
two three or so it won't be one two it
二三左右不会是一二
would be one two three as a set not
将是一二三不设置
really exactly in this in this order but
真的完全按照这个顺序
it will be always 1 2 3 2 3 1 3 2 1 and
它将始终是1 2 3 2 3 1 3 2 1和
so on however again this is an overhead
因此，这又是开销
because the natural order of the stream
因为流的自然顺序
the first three elements like four six
前三个元素，例如四个六个
one four four six four five and so on so
一四四六四有五等
whenever you do the limit and you have a
每当您达到极限并有一个
parallel stream like well think about it
像这样的并行流考虑一下
that maybe I don't really need the first
也许我真的不需要第一个
and element so just give it give it a
和元素，所以只要给它一个
hint that this is actually unordered I
暗示这实际上是无序的
don't care about the order so just give
不在乎订单，所以给
me just give me any element all right
我只要给我任何要素就好
yeah as a down-to-earth proof so we have
是的，作为扎实的证明，所以我们有
we have a bunch of numbers and we just
我们有一堆数字，我们只是
filter those that are bigger than the
过滤那些比
500 okay and if I invoke the find first
500好，如果我先调用查找
well the guy is smart it obeys it
这个家伙很聪明，它服从它
returns exactly the first the very first
刚好返回第一个
number that
那个
that is matching this condition however
符合这个条件
if I don't really care about about the
如果我真的不在乎
order if I'm interested in any this is
如果我对此感兴趣的话
what I'm doing here it's for for us four
我在这里做什么对我们四个人来说
times faster but of course it returns
倍快，但它当然会返回
the element that basically every time
基本上每次的元素
you invoke it it would be a different
您调用它会有所不同
one but depending how long you keep
一个，但要取决于您保留多长时间
invoking so again the owner unordered
再次调用所有者无序
and find any can be also your friend
并找到任何人也可以成为您的朋友
okay yeah avoiding short state so also
好吧，是的，避免短路状态
to think you think about an example so
想一想你这样的例子
imagine we have like a accumulator class
想象我们有一个累加器类
well all it does it's it's its
好吧，这是它的全部
accumulator so basically it has this
蓄电池，所以基本上它有这个
some method that you that you'll keep
您将保留的一些方法
that you keep invoking and it's simply
您一直在调用，这仅仅是
increasing the it's simply increasing
增加它只是增加
the result so right now if you do this
结果，现在就去做吧
if you do this kind of thing that you
如果你做这种事情，你
instantiate your accumulator and you try
实例化累加器，然后尝试
to invoke invoke this in parallel so
调用并行调用此
basically some of the numbers from 1 to
基本上是从1到
100 what you're gonna have different
100你将拥有不同
numbers all the time because you're
一直都是数字，因为你
going to have a race conditions all over
到处都有比赛条件
the place so again with parallel streams
这个地方再次与平行流
it's a kind of also try simply to
这也是一种尝试
unlearn certain certain patterns because
取消学习某些特定​​模式，因为
in this case when we have a function
在这种情况下，当我们有一个功能
that maintains a state it doesn't go so
保持状态不会这样
much so well along with the streams
与溪流一样好
which of course what you can do is to
当然可以做的是
make it is to make this method
使它成为这种方法
synchronized but actually well then all
同步但实际上一切都很好
day all day all the effort to have
全天全力以赴
parallel stream won't be water because
平行流不会是水，因为
they know the secret synchronize it's
他们知道秘密同步
very expensive when you have multi
当你有多的时候非常昂贵
course that they communicate with each
他们彼此沟通的过程
other saying ok do this no don't do this
其他说好吧做不做不做
because I'm doing something this is very
因为我正在做某件事，这非常
expensive so all your benefits of a
昂贵，所以您的所有好处
parallel stream will be will be lost
并行流将丢失
so basically lose like a reduction
所以基本上输掉了
function and again if you have parallel
函数，如果有并行则再次
streams stick to the stick to the pure
溪流坚持纯净的坚持
functions I'm sure there are plenty of
功能，我敢肯定有很多
lectures here about functional
关于功能的讲座
programming so whatever you learn those
编程，所以无论你学那些
there just apply it to parallel streams
在那里将其应用于并行流
okay almost at the end is the sequential
好吧，几乎在最后是顺序
sequential and parallel so as explained
顺序和并行，如前所述
we have this we have this well as stream
我们有这个我们有这样的流
is basically behaves like a builder
基本上就像一个建造者
pattern so it does really nothing till
模式，所以它实际上什么也没做
the very end when you involve when
当你介入的最后时刻
you're in when you call the boss the
你在打电话给老板的时候
terminal operation please just execute
终端操作请执行
me and you might be tempted by having
我和你可能会被吸引
those two methods that one is giving a
这两种方法给一个
hint okay when you arrive to the
当您到达时提示好
terminal operation though it's
终端操作虽然
sequential you the parallel one do it do
顺序执行并行操作
it do it in parallel so you might be
它并行执行，所以您可能会
like tempted okay maybe I could
像诱惑一样好吧，也许我可以
something could do something like this I
有些事情可以做这样的事情我
have a bunch of I have another range of
有很多我还有另一种
numbers in if I have a is if I'm
如果我有一个数字是如果我
computing primes it's expensive
计算素数昂贵
it costs time let's do it let's do it in
花费时间让我们做吧
let's do it in in parallel however when
让我们并行进行
I when I have my accumulator so you saw
我当我有我的蓄能器，所以你看到了
one slide before accumulators are evil
累积者邪恶之前的一张幻灯片
you cannot really do what you shouldn't
你真的不能做你不应该做的事
do it let's be smart and do it
做到这一点，让我们变得聪明起来吧
sequentially no it won't really work
依序不，它不会真正起作用
well it will work however the whole
很好，但是整个
stream will be invoked in a sequential
流将按顺序调用
way so you will lose the benefits of
这样您将失去的好处
parallelism okay sure
并行性好吗
shall I go back
我可以回去吗
it's it's it's it's a very good question
这是一个很好的问题
well this is just a matter of fact it's
嗯，这只是事实，
it is like this but they are they are
就是这样，但是他们是
however libraries that you can kind of
但是您可以使用的库
overcome it that you can that you can
克服它，你可以，你可以
achieve a fine graced find a grained
达到优雅的目的
control what is it parallel what is what
控制什么是并行什么是什么
is not we can speak gladly about it and
是不是我们可以高兴地谈论这件事，
actually I couldn't know you simply well
其实我根本不认识你
in yeah yeah so you really well if you
是的，如果你真的很好
stick to the pure JDK 8 so not some
坚持纯JDK 8，所以不
other library libraries on top of it I
我上面的其他图书馆
would probably split it or just get rid
可能会分裂或摆脱
of the accumulator to have like a
蓄能器的像
reduction or something but yeah it's a
减少之类的东西，但是是的
it's something also I'm personally
这也是我个人的东西
missing so we can all right so almost at
失踪了，所以我们可以没事了，几乎在
the end
结束
sorry checking the time all the time in
很抱歉，一直在检查时间
our coming from Switzerland a lot the
我们来自瑞士很多
length of watches so well you have to
手表的长度如此之好，你必须
keep checking it alright so I think that
继续检查它，所以我认为
the main conclusion is because making a
主要结论是因为
parallel stream is so easy
并行流是如此简单
well it's so easy to turn your parallel
好吧，平行转动很容易
streams you stream to parallel stream it
流到并行流
doesn't mean you should do it on the
并不意味着您应该在
contrary it's always just do it wisely
相反，总是明智地做
and well if you have like a application
如果您有喜欢的应用程序
that has like I don't know if it's big a
好像我不知道这有多大
big chunk of it is a parallel stream
它的很大一部分是并行流
does does something apply always those
是否有一些东西总是适用于那些
three steps which is measure measure and
三个步骤是衡量措施和
measure to find out whether it really
衡量是否真的
behaves as it should because you you
表现得应该是因为你
might you might find that okay
也许你会觉得还好
underperforming or it completely does
表现不佳或完全做到了
something wrong so use it for CPU
出现问题，因此将其用于CPU
intensive tasks choose data structure
密集任务选择数据结构
that are easy to decompose for example
容易分解的例子
link is linked list is not choose data
链接被链接列表不是选择数据
structures that are also easy to compose
也很容易组成的结构
I mean link list it's easy to compose
我的意思是链接列表很容易撰写
but if you think about the heart set if
但是如果你考虑一下心脏
you have like a collector scooping by
你就像一个收集者sc着
they are not so trivial
他们不是那么琐碎
to compose again so think about it and
再次撰写，请三思而后行
rather prefer it for a big set of data
宁愿使用它来获取大量数据
so you have like I don't know ten
所以你就像我不知道十
elements in your stream don't bother
流中的元素不会打扰
well thank you very much for being an
好，非常感谢您成为
awesome audience and have a blast in
真棒观众，并在
direct well first
直接先井